ABOUT

I'm a Frontend Developer with two years of experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development and proactive feature optimization.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Dorothy

Frontend Developer | Jun 2021 - Present

- Frontend development of different company products.
- I identify and fix bugs/technical issues before and after deploying.
- I implemented Redux and Context API for state management (depending on the project needs).
- I am an active team member with UIUX knowledge working on the redesign of our products.
- Contributing ideas on new features and improvements.
- Tech stack: NextJs (ReactJs Framework), Redux.

Freelance

Frontend Developer | Jun 2020 - May 2021

- A freelance project for a Graphic and Typeface designer is a responsive website built in NextJs.
- I worked closely with the designer.
- Tech stack: NextJs . See the project here.

Cabin Crew

Emirates | May 2016 - Jul 2020

Workforce Management Analyst

Telefónica | Dec 2014 - Apr 2016

- Analyzed, controlled, and managed the services in the Customer Service Department.
- Executed actions and launched the contingency plan for any situation that may impact Customer Service performance.

Workforce Management Analyst

Directv | Dec 2014 - Apr 2013 - Dec 2014

- My work consisted of controlling in real-time the behavior of the Customer Service Center's traffic calls.
- Ensured compliance with a high service level.
- Created reports about customer service agent's performance. I Solved problems that affected the business.

Customer Care

Directv | Apr 2010 - Apr 2013 - Dec 2014

• Customer Care Support.

SKILLS:

- HTML5
- CSS
- Javascript (ES6)
- Redux
- Nextis
- Reactjs

- Testing and Debugging.
- Browser developer tools.
- Responsive Design
- Git, Github

EDUCATION:

Mar 2020 - Jul 2020 | Courselt, Buenos Aires

Frontend development coding bootcamp with an extension of +200 hours.